[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Senate", "House of Representatives"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NN", "EX", ":", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "Is it as simple as, sorry, you are Republicans, we didn't like the bill -- we're Democrats, we're not having it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "It's not that simple because they have to come up, Piers, with some sort of compromise, they have to come up with come sort of plan that can pass the Senate and but then go back to the House of Representatives and pass there -- something that the president could sign that would allow the United States to raise the debt ceiling and avert some sort of financial disaster come Tuesday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Jessica, it's been a day of frantic arm twisting, but we've ended up really absolutely nowhere, haven't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jessica"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "PERSON": ["Boehner"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Senator Durbin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I'm sure you recall the speech that was given to the American people on Monday night by Speaker Boehner.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Durbin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Schumer"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What is your contingency plan if this doesn't get through the Senate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Oh, I think Senator Schumer laid that out pretty clearly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "I know you're calling for Leader McConnell to come to the table and negotiate, but what is the way forward from here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "It's up to the Republicans.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["McConnell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBO"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Are all of the increased savings due to (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "CBO has come up with those numbers and I told you before, we have laid out all the numbers, you can dissect them, look at them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "And I heard a report earlier and maybe you can confirm this, that Speaker Boehner and the president haven't actually exchanged a single word in five days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "I mean, you are so way out of step with public opinion, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Well, it's nice no chat with you, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "It doesn't even get debated, don't you think, Piers, that's a little unreasonable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "No, I think what they think is unreasonable, is not a question of being partisan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "How exactly do you guys expect this country's economy to recover?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, what you do is you look at House Republicans, twice, not once, but twice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Republican Party"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Where are we with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, there's clearly, Piers, an internal battle going on within the Republican Party right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Where is that compromise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "What's been happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "No, I don't think Speaker Boehner has lost any of his power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Who is taking responsibility for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I'll tell you this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["64 percent", "47 percent"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, it's kind of interesting that you say 64 percent are willing to raise taxes when we know that 47 percent of wage earning households in America don't even pay taxes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Finally, Allen West, should we go to default here, an unprecedented catastrophe in the history of America, who has to resign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, I'm not looking for anyone to resign.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Allen West"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "But would it be a massive blow to the Democrats or more of a blow to Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "I think it will be a blow to both, probably roughly equal, depending on how you look at it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How would do you that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "If I could have my way, cut, cap and balance would be law of the land.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Are you aware of the rising sentiment around the world that this is looking fairly shameful for the American political process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Look, we're a democracy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, I actually think there are three things going on that make for high drama and a lot of frustration, as you have been describing on your program.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "He has a point, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Well, I think there are many Republicans who oppose balanced budget.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Business booming, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, you know, we're a pizza company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "You're a bipartisan operation, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How many pizzas did you actually deliver last night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Last night was a relatively good-sized order, 20 pizzas up to Representative Boehner.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Is he on the spicy side of life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "You know, that's a good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110729pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "And did they pay cash or credit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I believe it was credit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]